So as you were saying before, Tableau is really good for exploring data.
正如你之前提到的 Tableau 非常善于探索数据
So I was wondering,
我想知道
as a Tableau professional, could you show us how you explore a data set?
作为 Tableau 专业人士 你能展示下你是如何探索数据集的吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, sure, and there are a lot of different ways to explore data.
—-好的 我们可以通过多种不同的方式探索数据
But one of the ways that I like to start is just by asking questions.
我喜欢的一种方式是提出问题
And so actually,
这是一个
I have a dataset here in-front of me that shows the top grossing movies.
关于最卖座电影的数据集
And we have a number of different ways that we can explore the data.
我们可以通过多种不同的方式探索这些数据
For example we have directors, genres, the movie title,
例如 其中包含导演 类型 电影名称
we have the budget and the profit.
预算和利润
So actually I'm curious about directors and the profits that they brought in.
我对导演和电影带来的利润感兴趣
So I'm going to take this dimension of director.
所以我将选择这个“Director”维度
I'm going to drag it here onto my viz.
将其拖到我的可视化图表上
And then I'm going to find profit and drag it over here and sort this.
然后找到“Profit”并拖到这里并进行排序
And now I can start to see,
现在可以看到
okay, here are some directors, then how much money they made.
这是一些导演 他们带来了多少利润
Now, I'm kind of curious about Peter Jackson actually, and
我对 Peter Jackson 比较感兴趣
so I am going to keep only Peter Jackson.
所以我只留下 Peter Jackson
So I'm essentially filtering out all of the other directors and
我实际上滤除了所有其他导演
I can see that his movies generated quite a lot of profit.
可以看到他的电影带来了大量票房收入
But which movies are we talking about here?
但是我们讨论的是哪些电影呢？
So I'm actually going to take the movie title and I'm going to drag it here.
我将找到“Movie Title”并拖到这里
And here I can see all the movies that he made over time.
从这里可以看到他导演过的所有电影
Now, I'm also interested in when these movies are made.
我还想知道这些电影拍摄于什么时候
So, I have the release date that I will also drag over here.
所以找到发行日期并拖到这里
Okay great, so now we have it sorted from 2001 to 2014.
按照从 2001 到 2014 的顺序排序
Now, I don't really care about King Kong or The Lovely Bones,
我不想研究《金刚》和《可爱的骨头》
so we're just going to exclude those two and
所以排除这两部电影
now we get to compare The Lord of the Rings versus The Hobbit.
现在将《指环王》与《霍比特人》进行对比
Now which set of movies, which trilogy, is better?
哪个系列（哪个三部曲）更棒？
And this is a conversation that we have in the office, right, which is better,
我们讨论的是票房 哪个票房更高？
Lord of the Rings or The Hobbit?
《指环王》还是《霍比特人》？
And now we have data to quantitatively answer this question of which is better.
我们可以根据量化数据回答这一问题
So we have the profits that we're looking on here, and
这里是利润
we can see that the profits of The Lord of the Rings went up over time and
可以看出《指环王》系列一部比一部票房高
the Hobbit profits actually kind of went down over time.
而《霍比特人》实际上票房下滑了
But how much did it cost to make these movies anyway?
但是拍摄这些电影要多少成本呢？
We're just looking at how much they brought in.
我们只看到了它们带来的收入
Now we also have the budget that we can look at, so
现在我们还可以查看预算
let's move the budget over here.
所以将“Budget”移到这里
And now in just a minute or so
我只花了一分钟左右的时间
I've been able to find out something really interesting.
就发现了一个很有趣的现象
Which is that while the budget of Lord of the Rings went down, the profits kept
虽然《指环王》的预算降低了
going up and the budget for The Hobbit was actually quite a lot higher, but
利润却一直上升 《霍比特人》的预算要高很多
over time the profits went down.
但是利润却下降了
So Tableau is a really easy way to quickly drag and
所以 Tableau 可以轻松快速地
drop different elements and explore data and
拖放不同的元素和探索数据
view it in a number of different ways and start answering questions.
并以各种不同的方式查看数据和回答问题
&gt;&gt; And win bets with your friends.
—-并且与好友打赌并获胜
&gt;&gt; And win bets with your friends, most importantly.
—-最重要的是 与好友打赌获胜